So we've talked about the simple past.
所以我们讨论了简单的过去。
We've talked about the past progressive or continuous.
我们已经讨论过过去进行式或连续式。
We've talked about present perfect.
我们已经讨论过现在完成时。
Now we need to talk about past perfect.
现在我们需要谈谈过去完成时。
This one is a little bit difficult.
这个有点难。
So we have to use a lot of examples to kind of get the feeling for it.
所以我们必须使用很多例子来感受它。
However we can make it a little easier by saying that it's grammatically similar to the present perfect
但是，我们可以说它在语法上与现在完成时相似，从而使它更容易一些
where we say have for example I have been the only change we make is saying had been had been going
例如，我们所说的我是我们所做的唯一改变就是说一直在进行
instead of have been going OK or we can say I had finished I had finished doesn't have to be i n g so
而不是一直很好，或者我们可以说我已经完成了 我已经完成了
that way it's similar to the present perfect tense the one we did before but when we use it is a little
这样它类似于我们之前做的现在完成时，但是当我们使用它时有点
bit more complicated it can be used to express what I call a past of a past if you want to use it in
稍微复杂一点，如果你想用它来表达我称之为过去的过去
the same way as the present perfect where it goes up to some point it's like that but then that point
就像现在的完美一样，它上升到某个点
is not the present not now it's in the past and now is over here.
不是现在，不是现在，是过去，现在是过去。
So that's a little bit complicated but I'll give you some examples in a minute.
所以这有点复杂，但我会在一分钟内给你一些例子。
We can also say just like we did with the present perfect tense we can also say that something happened
我们也可以说就像我们对现在完成时所做的那样，我们也可以说发生了某事
a certain number of times or something happened or didn't happen before.
一定次数或某事发生或未发生过。
Another thing that happened in the past and now is over here.
过去和现在发生的另一件事在这里。
So this happened and this happened and then here's last Tuesday and then this is now.
所以这发生了，这发生了，然后是上周二，然后是现在。
All right.
好的。
So it's two things happened before this happened.
所以在这件事发生之前发生了两件事。
Totally it's three things but two things happened before that.
总共是三件事，但在那之前发生了两件事。
So let's look at some pretty simple examples with this past perfect tense.
因此，让我们看一些过去完成时的非常简单的例子。
I had been going to the gym every day until I got my new job.
在我找到新工作之前，我每天都去健身房。
I had been.
我曾。
So that thing was going on.
所以事情就这样发生了。
It's like saying I have been going to the gym every day.
这就像说我每天都去健身房一样。
I have been would mean that it's going on now.
我一直意味着它现在正在发生。
But I got my new job maybe a month ago and so it stopped when I got my new job.
但我大概一个月前得到了新工作，所以当我得到新工作时它就停止了。
So now I'm not going to the gym.
所以现在我不去健身房了。
It stopped in the past.
它停在过去。
I have been going to the gym up until now.
到目前为止，我一直在去健身房。
I had been going to the gym up until a past point I had been going to the gym every day until I got
我一直去健身房，直到过去我每天都去健身房，直到我得到
my new job.
我的新工作。
Now.
现在。
OK.
好的。
How long had you been waiting.
你等了多久。
Before I arrived.
在我到达之前。
This should be at BGF Sorry.
这应该在 BGF 对不起。
Sorry.
对不起。
How long had you been waiting.
你等了多久。
Before I arrived.
在我到达之前。
OK.
好的。
So I arrived at 2 p.m..
所以我是下午2点到的。。
Now it's 5:00 p.m. It's over here 5 p.m. now.
现在是下午 5:00。下午5点到了现在。
This is 2:00 p.m. OK.
这是下午 2:00好的。
And you are waiting for me right.
而你正在等我对。
I have been waiting.
我一直在等待。
If you arrive and I'm sitting here I'll say I've been waiting up until the present.
如果你到了，我坐在这里，我会说我一直等到现在。
Right now I've been waiting for an hour.
现在我已经等了一个小时了。
Oh I'm sorry but this is in the past 2:00 p.m..
哦，对不起，这是在过去的下午 2:00。
How long had you been waiting.
你等了多久。
Before I arrived.
在我到达之前。
How long had you been waiting before I arrived so you can think of it in a similar way to the other
在我到达之前你等了多久，所以你可以像其他人一样思考它
one we learned.
我们学到的一个。
But you just push the present back into the past.
但你只是把现在推回过去。
And now we have a a now here.
现在我们在这里有了一个 now。
Right.
正确的。
But basically the idea is the same.
但基本上思路是一样的。
I hope that's clear.
我希望这很清楚。
But we'll go over a couple more examples anyway.
但无论如何，我们将再举几个例子。
OK.
好的。
So a few more examples here.
所以还有几个e这里的例子。
We had been friends we had been friends for many years until we started at different high schools.
在我们开始在不同的高中开始之前，我们一直是多年的朋友。
So that means now are we friends.
所以这意味着我们现在是朋友了。
No no we're not probably not friends anymore.
不不，我们可能不再是朋友了。
We had been friends we had been best friends until we started at different high schools.
在我们开始在不同的高中开始之前，我们一直是最好的朋友。
We started at different high schools maybe 15 years ago 15 years ago we started at different high schools.
我们可能在 15 年前开始在不同的高中 15 年前我们在不同的高中开始。
We had been very very good friends up until then.
在那之前，我们一直是非常非常好的朋友。
OK.
好的。
Can we say we were very good friends until high school.
我们可以说我们在高中之前是非常好的朋友吗？
Past tense.
过去式。
Yeah yeah.
是啊。
You can you can say that in this case.
在这种情况下，您可以这样说。
But sometimes it makes it more clear to use this past perfect tense.
但有时使用过去完成时更清楚。
I had seen the movie once already but went again and then we could say maybe last night because why.
我已经看过这部电影了，但又去了一次，然后我们可以说可能是昨晚，因为为什么。
Because I really liked it well I really like it.
因为我真的很喜欢它，我真的很喜欢它。
You still like it so you can use that too.
你仍然喜欢它，所以你也可以使用它。
So on Tuesday I saw the movie the first time.
所以周二我第一次看这部电影。
Wow.
哇。
Such a good movie.
这么好的电影。
Right.
正确的。
And then last night I went another time because I enjoyed it.
然后昨晚我又去了一次，因为我喜欢它。
Now it's maybe three days later.
现在可能是三天后。
So I have seen the movie.
所以我看过这部电影。
How many times.
多少次。
Totally.
完全。
I have seen it twice.
我已经看过两次了。
But when I want to talk about seeing it the last time I saw it.
但是当我想谈论看到它时，我最后一次看到它。
All right three days ago I saw it most recently three days ago and then talk about how many times before
好吧三天前我最近看到的三天前然后说说之前多少次
that past thing I saw it one time then I would say I had seen it once already but went again last night
过去的事情我看过一次然后我会说我已经看过一次但昨晚又去了
for three days ago in my other example not trying to confuse you there.
三天前，在我的另一个例子中，并没有试图让你感到困惑。
How about this.
这个怎么样。
I went to Canada.
我去了加拿大。
I went to Canada on Monday.
我星期一去了加拿大。
I had already been there three times OK.
我已经去过那里三遍了。
So how many times have I been to Canada four.
那么我去过加拿大多少次了，四次。
I had already been there three times before I went there on Monday.
在星期一去之前，我已经去过那里三次了。
Now I'm not there.
现在我不在了。
Now I'm back where I live right.
现在我回到了我住的地方。
So we basically are talking about past things that happened before another past thing.
所以我们基本上是在谈论在另一件过去的事情之前发生的过去的事情。
I went to Canada on Monday.
我星期一去了加拿大。
I had been there three times before.
我以前去过那里三次。
OK let's try another example.
好的，让我们试试另一个例子。
I had asked her to wait for me but when I came outside she was gone.
我曾让她等我，但当我走到外面时，她已经走了。
So we could just say I came outside and she was gone.
所以我们可以说我出去了，她走了。
That's a simple past thing that happened right.
这是一件简单的过去发生的事情。
Simple past.
一般过去时。
I came outside and she was gone.
我走到外面，她走了。
But if I want to give that more detail and I want to express more about the whole situation I can talk
但如果我想提供更多细节，我想表达更多关于整个情况的信息，我可以谈谈
about what I did before I came outside and saw that she was gone.
关于我在外面看到她走了之前我做了什么。
Well what did I do before that.
那么在那之前我做了什么。
I asked her to wait for me outside.
我让她在外面等我。
So I want to express a past thing that happened before another past thing.
所以我想表达在另一件过去的事情之前发生的过去的事情。
That's when it's really really useful to use past perfect tense.
那时使用过去完成时真的非常有用。
I had asked her to wait for me but when I got outside or when I came outside she was gone.
我曾让她等我，但当我到外面或外面时，她已经走了。
Now we have a really clear picture of the whole thing that happened in many cases using this style of
现在我们对使用这种风格的许多情况下发生的整个事情有了一个非常清晰的认识。
grammar using this tense makes it really clear.
使用这种时态的语法使它非常清楚。
The difficulty is how do you do it right.
困难在于你如何正确地做到这一点。
Getting enough practice is really important so you can get the feel for how to use this more difficult
获得足够的练习真的很重要，这样你才能感觉到如何更难地使用它
type of grammar this more difficult tense.
这类语法这种时态比较难。123
So practice it.
所以练习一下。
I'll provide the examples.
我将提供示例。
Make sure you review those really carefully.
确保你真的仔细审查了这些。
Lots of examples are a great way to get the feeling for something but it's also very important to do
很多例子是了解某事的好方法，但做起来也很重要
lots of practice because then it can become a habit.
大量的练习，因为那样它就可以成为一种习惯。
And when you want to express yourself it's right there.
当你想表达自己时，它就在那里。
All right.
好的。
So an assignment to practice this make at least two sentences with each tense each.
因此，练习这个的作业至少要有两个句子，每个句子的每个时态。
Each one we learned the simple past the past progressive right was going the present perfect and the
我们每个人都学会了简单的过去过去的进步的权利正在走向现在的完美和
past perfect practice.
过去的完美实践。
All of the different types make two sentences or more.
所有不同的类型都构成两个或更多的句子。
Don't worry too much about remembering the names right.
不要太担心记住正确的名字。
Focus on the examples that I gave you in this lesson.
专注于我在本课中给你的例子。
And then just make sure you feel really comfortable using each one you need to get comfortable with
然后确保你在使用每一个你需要感到舒服的时候感觉真的很舒服
it.
它。
If you do you'll be able to express things in time wherever you are especially in the past which is
如果你这样做了，无论你身在何处，你都能够及时地表达事物，尤其是在过去，即
the most difficult.
最困难的。
You'll be able to do those things really easily and that will give you a lot of power because when you
你将能够非常轻松地做这些事情，这会给你很大的力量，因为当你
speak people will go Oh well I understand exactly what you're saying.
说话的人会走哦，我完全明白你在说什么。
You have command over time.
随着时间的推移，你有指挥权。
Practice is really important.
实践真的很重要。
And so I hope you practice a lot.
所以我希望你多练习。
And if it's boring just remember you know it's gonna get more interesting it's going to get more fun.
如果它很无聊，请记住你知道它会变得更有趣，它会变得更有趣。
All right.
好的。